<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WakaBirb</string>
    <string name="musicOnKey">musicOnKey</string>
    <string name="Music">Enable Music</string>
    <string name="MusicCheckboxSummary">Uncheck to turn background music off</string>
    <string name="seOnKey">seOnKey</string>
    <string name="SoundEffects">Enable Sound Effects</string>
    <string name="SoundEffectsCheckboxSummary">Uncheck to turn sound effects off</string>
    <string name ="MusicCatTitle">Music Settings</string>
    <string name="OtherSettings">Other Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="settings">Birb Settings</string>
    <string name="other_stuff">Birb Stuff</string>
    <string name="results">RESULTS</string>
    <string name="play_again">Play Again?</string>
    <string name="waka_birb">WAKA BIRB</string>
    <string name="enter_your_user_name">Enter your user name</string>
    <string name="start_game">Start Game</string>
    <string name="google_play_sign_in">Google Play Sign In</string>
    <string name="sign_in_to_google_play_games_to_post_your_scores_to_the_leaderboard">Sign in to Google Play Games to post your scores to the leaderboard</string>
    <string name="coming_soon">COMING SOON</string>
    <string name="waka_birb_shirt">Waka_birb_shirt</string>
    <string name="waka_birb_merchanise">Waka Birb Merchandise</string>
    <string name="birb_history">Birb History</string>
    <string name="purple_birb">Purple Birb</string>
    <string name="red_birb">Red Birb</string>
    <string name="Click">CLICK</string>
    <string name="white_waka_birb_t_shirt">white waka birb t-shirt</string>
    <string name="waka_birb_apparel">Waka Birb Apparel</string>
    <string name="also_by_hnb_enterprise">Also by HnB Enterprise:</string>
    <string name="like_birbs">Like Birbs</string>
    <string name="history">BIRB HISTORY</string>
    <string name="historyWriteUp">
        A long time ago, in a land far far away, a group of computer programmers were working on a project.
        This project involved a system for feeding birds.
        There were many birds wanting to be fed but only 5 birds could be inside the feeding area at time.
        Therefore the programmers had to devise a mechanism that would allow the birds to notify the feeding area that they were hungry.
        \n \n
        While working on this mechanism, many problems came about.
        Sometimes too many birds would get into the feeding area.
        Sometimes the birds would not leave the feeding area.
        Sometimes the birds would leave the feeding area, but not indicate they had left.
        Sometimes the birds would not enter the feeding area, even when empty.
        Sometimes the birds would not notify the feeding area when they were hungry.
        After working on this project for many hours and days without rest, the programmers started to go crazy and were very tired.
        After typing the word \'bird\' over and over during all this, they started to misspell bird, especially when typing very fast.
        Bird became birb.
        \n \n
        Now, computer programmers are not very artist people and can not draw very well, especially when tired and crazy.
        But they needed to have pictures of the feeding process to assist them in keeping the stages correct.
        They did their very best to draw a bird, but it was not entirely bird like. It was rather unproportional.
        Its legs and wings were small for its overly large body.
        The programmers also drew accessories on these birds, to keep track of which bird was which.
        And we all know that real birds do not wear accessories or clothes.
        This, with the pictures of these \'birds\' posted everywhere, with their sleep deprivation, and their typing birb over and over, is how birbs were created.
        Now birbs appear everywhere. They can be found on whiteboards, in games, in chat, and many many other places.
    </string>
</resources>
